# ANGEL DANIEL ANGELES TORIBIO

Santo Domingo, 10205 | 8296522807 | daniel\_1234@hotmail.es

### Summary

Software Engineer with 7 years of experience in TI. Actually I've been working on Argentum since 2015 developing .Net web (JS) projects, using docker, linux/windows, sql server and more. In parallel I'm working as React, Nodejs Developer and AWS serverless on a software project called LityStyles and other freelancers projects.

### **Experience**

# **Full Stack Software Developer**

01/2015 to Current

### **Argentum Inc**

- Maintenance to 3 applications adding changes such as autosave in stepper, payments and others.
- Decrease 80% of the waiting time in queries of thousands of documents in the system.
- Implementing pipelines for execution of functional tests increase in the agility of the testing processes from 20% to 55%.
- Development of backlog pending tasks in three months (devoting extra time), increasing user satisfaction from 50% to 80%.
- Updates of applications and SQL servers for applications used by more than 300 users.

### React/Nodejs Developer

03/2022 to 08/2023

#### **Freelance**

- Dockerizing applications for production and development versions.
- integration of external services for content searches inchatGPT translation and publication of content in wordpress.
- State management with asynchronous processes in views and tables, generating a better user experience in receiving results.

# **React/AWS Serverless Developer**

09/2020 to 03/2022

# Litystyles

- Development of Web and Mobile application for the automation of processes in barbershops and salons (in pilot plan).
- Fixing 5+ production bugs based on troubleshooting non-relational database queries with GraphQI.
- Deployment of mobile application in Google Play and App Store fulfilling the high requirements and standards of Apple and Android.
- Firebase Cloud Messaging integration for notifications, AWS Serverless for backend (Appsync, Cognito, DynamoDB, Lambda, etc...) and Google OAuth for federated authentication.

React/NodeJS Developer 11/2022 to 03/2023

#### SnapBrillia

- Development of a Web and Backend application for the management of resource management for projects, achieving 90% project management satisfaction.
- Correction of +20 reported bug fixes, development of 3 business processes
- Automation of the resource request process with payment project.

### **Skills**

- Languages: Javascript, Python, C#
- Frameworks: React, Nodejs, Typescript, DRF, Jest
- Databases: Postgres, SQL Server, DynamoDB, Mongo
- Others: Docker, Git, AWS Serverless.
- Patterns: OOP, TDD, Functional Programming
- OS: Windows, Linux, IOS

# **Education**

**Bachelor of Science: Software Engineer** 

2019

Diploma of Higher Education: Software Technology

Santo Domingo **2015** 

ITLA

Santo Domingo Este

Languages

Spanish: First Language

English:

В1

Intermediate

**UNAPEC** 

# **Additional Information**

• Portfolio | aangeles.com